Guide to the Deep Dish TV Records MSS.312
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Video Productions, 1982-2018; 13.5 Linear Feet in 17 manuscript boxes and 5 flat boxes; 906 MiniDV; 470 U-matic; 93 1_Inch_Video_Reel; 81 Betacam_SP; 26 Betacam; 58 DVCAM; 27 VHS; 5 Hi8; 3 audiocassettes; 1.538 Terabytes in 6,117 files
  - Clip Compilation, Undated (Box 152, Minidv 312_1259)
    Content includes Arab Jobeer village; Lawyer interview; Bombing of a shop in Fallujah, kill man and son; young man killed and brother disabled
  - Clip Compilation, Undated (Box 150, Minidv 312_1158)
    Content includes Family recounts events of shooting, Part II; Medea interviews brother; Squatter family at entrance to National Theater
  - Clip Compilation -- Brian Drolet Demonstration, Undated (Box 151, Minidv 312_1201)
  - Clip Compilation -- DC, Undated (Box 152, Minidv 312_1214)
    Content includes Meet the Press; Reclaim the Streets DC; Eve of 40th March; Sorry State of the Union
  - Clip Compilation -- Palestinian Strike, Undated (Box 150, Minidv 312_1155)
    Content includes Palestinian Strike; Interview with employee; visit to oil tanker and captain's home; Telecom bombed building
  - Clip Compilation and Interviews, Undated (Box 134, U-matic 312_1115)
    Content includes Rest of Faye Williams Interview; Loading trucks - all the women work hand in hand; Driving in Baghdad and interview with driver saying we don't need these sanctions; Minister of Health
  - Clip Compilation and Interviews, January 13-14 (Box 134, U-matic 312_1116)
    Content includes Bakaa - Palestinian refugee; Camp in Amman, Jordan; interview with Palestinian Aysha Odar living in Jordan; Brenda loading trucks and january 13 at Federation of Jordanian Women's Office, intro and questions, sound with echo, ends midway
  - CNN CPAC, Undated (Box 134, Dvcam 312_1054)
  - CODEPINK and Billionaires for Bush Rally, Undated (Box 153, Minidv 312_1284)
    From Mark Dworkin
  - CODEPINK Clip Reel, Undated (Box 150, Minidv 312_1135)
    Content includes Anwar; Dr. Manzar (Cancer Ward); Police Chief; Demonstration; Squatter's Compound; Shia Women's Circle
  - CODEPINK Interview with Susan Galleymore, Undated (Box 150, Minidv 312_1125)
    Content includes mother of US soldier serving in Iraq. Member of Codepink delegation.
  - CODEPINK at Riverside, Undated (Box 153, Minidv 312_1286)
  - CODEPINK Master, Undated (Box 151, Minidv 312_1212)
  - CODEPINK, Undated (Box 150, Minidv 312_1159)
    Content includes Capital Steps, Supreme Court, Olga Vives
  - Columbus Area Prisons, Undated (Box 129, U-matic 312_0584)
  - Committee for Open Discussion of Zionism, September 18 (Box 148, Minidv 312_0943, 312_0944)
  - Connections: Grassroots Views of the Changing World -- Production File, Undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - "Conscientious Objection: An Interview with Camilo Mejra and the Public", Undated; cuid39516 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_384)
  - Crime Show Studio Shoot, Undated (Box 130, U-matic 312_0598)
    With Janine Jackson
  - "Crimes Against Humanity", Undated (Box 147, Minidv 312_0862)
  - David Barsimian in Cairo, Talking About Alternative Media, Undated (Box 153, Minidv 312_1282)
    Content includes Speech on US Media and propaganda; media doesn't challenge government; imperialism; independent media, how it is funded; development of alternative media in Cairo; young people creating independent media; shots of posters on walls; Q and A; situation of Arabs in US
  - David Barsamian Interview with Wolf, Undated (Box 156, Minidv 312_1512, 312_1513)
  - David Harvey B-roll, Undated (Box 155, Minidv 312_1430)
  - "Dead or Behind Bars" (Versions A and B), "Allegations", Undated (Box 130, U-matic 312_0603)
  - "Decorative Protest," "American Dream", Undated (Box 156, Minidv 312_1493)
  - Deep Dish Theme Music, Undated (Box 147, U-matic 312_0891)
  - Democratic National Convention -- Music Cut-away, Undated (Box 138, Dvcam 312_1420)
  - "Do the Write Thing", Undated (Box 157, Minidv 312_1539)
  - Dr. Rashad on KOMU-TV, Columbia, MO, Undated (Box 134, Vhs 312_1041)
  - Dub of E-Butane, Undated (Box 159, Minidv 312_1677)
  - Edit Workshop, "Lay Off to This," "So Far: BethAnn and Priscilla", Undated (Box 156, Minidv 312_1525)
  - Elizabeth T., Undated (Box 156, Minidv 312_1484)
  - FAIR Interviews, Undated (Box 155, Hi8 312_1423)
    Subject is Corporate Ownership/Sponsorship
  - "The Fight Is Elsewhere", Undated (Box 138, Vhs 312_1731)
    Directed by Norma Castillo
  - Footage of March at UFPJ, Undated (Box 152, Minidv 312_1267)
    With Brendan Schwartz
  - "Four More Years", Undated (Box 135, U-matic 312_1389)
  - "Free Speech vs the FCC", Undated; cuid39414 (Box 137, Vhs 312_1412)
  - "Freedom of Invasion" Rough Cut, Undated (Box 155, Minidv 312_1429)
  - Freedom of Speech on Trial -- "Part One: Geoffrey Blank and the No Police State Coalition", Undated; cuid39517 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_385)
  - From Archives Shoot, Undated (Box 147, Minidv 312_0873)
  - Gazwan Mkhtar, Medea in Amman, Undated (Box 151, Minidv 312_1179)
  - "Gender and Sexuality in US Capitalism", Undated (Box 148, Minidv 312_0952, 312_0953)
    With Left Forum
  - Green Party Rally, Washington Square, Undated (Box 153, Minidv 312_1274)
  - Guillermo Gomez Pena, Undated (Box 132, U-matic 312_0977)
  - "Global Village or Global Pillage", Undated (Box 126, U-matic 312_0552)
  - Halliday, Dahr, Undated (Box 159, Minidv 312_1688)
  - Hez Official Presser Funeral, Undated (Box 149, Minidv 312_1064)
  - "Hollywood Victory: Delusions of a Maverick as President", Undated (Box 152, Minidv 312_1226)
    From Paper Tiger TV; Content includes Scenes of Bush on fighter carrier cut with movie scenes; then scenes from kids at a camp, completely unrelated interviews
  - "The Hour of Sunlight", Undated (Box 156, Minidv 312_1475, 312_1482)
  - "How History Was Wounded", Undated (Box 137, Vhs 312_1410)
  - Housing, Undated (Box 156, Minidv 312_1497)
  - Howard Zinn -- Columbus Day, Undated (Box 147, Minidv 312_0876)
    Content includes shots of parade, flags, interviews about history, Columbus, with Schoolhouse History Rock; Shot by Felipe
  - Howard Zinn / Fred Jerome Interview, Undated (Box 147, Minidv 312_0866)
  - Howard Zinn Interview #1, Undated (Box 134, U-matic 312_1038, 312_1039)
    From Carla Leshne, PTTV/Mission Creek
  - Howard Zinn on Labor (Cut-aways), Undated (Box 147, Minidv 312_0865)
    Content includes Zinn on strikes, Goldman, Jones, Haywood
  - Howard Zinn -- Louise Levi, Ya Ya, Undated (Box 147, Minidv 312_0874)
  - "The Impossible Dream?" by Michela Smith, Undated; cuid39521 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_389)
    Produced by Last Minute
  - "Insecure Communities: Families Under Threat", Undated; cuid39519 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_387)
    Short film about the "Secure Communities" ICE policy that was in place from 2013-2017; Directed by Angad Bhalla, produced by Judson Memorial Church, the New Sanctuary Coalition of New York and the Center for Constitutional Rights
  - Interview with Elizabeth and Daniel, Undated (Box 156, Minidv 312_1476)
  - Interview with Entisar Rae Aseel, Undated (Box 150, Minidv 312_1108, 312_1109, 312_1110)
    Tape label notes: "No Audio"
  - Interview with General Secretary ICP and GC Member, Undated (Box 151, Minidv 312_1176)
  - Interviews, Undated (Box 147, Minidv 312_0919)
  - Interviews, Undated (Box 149, Minidv 312_1010)
  - Iraqi Arrests, Undated (Box 148, Minidv 312_0932)
    Content includes Scenes of soldiers making arrests and Iraqi Prisoners
  - Iraqis Tortured by American Soldiers, Undated (Box 151, Minidv 312_1188)
    Duration: 7 minutes
    May contain graphic content
  - Janis Karpinksi, Undated (Box 148, Minidv 312_0940)
  - "Jesse Dyen's Song," Homeless Shelter, Undated (Box 147, Minidv 312_0887)
  - Juliano Memorial, Undated (Box 156, Minidv 312_1508)
  - Jury, Undated (Box 160, Minidv 312_1720)
  - Kashmir US Congress Hearing, Undated (Box 152, Minidv 312_1228)
  - "Keep Hope Alive" Source, Undated (Box 126, U-matic 312_0551)
  - "Know Your Rights", Undated; cuid39520 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_388)
    Short film by the Coalition for Humane Immigrant Rights of Los Angeles (CHIRLA)
  - Koewen, Undated (Box 147, Minidv 312_0868)
  - Lamia Interview, Undated (Box 150, Minidv 312_1143, 312_1144)
    Content includes Scoping out CNN, and old US embassy; Vigil - smoking gun in the van discussion; Babylon; interview with Lamia describes the 1991 bombing and waiting for this bombing; Mesopotamia
  - Last Words from Jose and Martha, Undated (Box 162, Minidv 312_1970)
  - Les McCann, Undated (Box 155, Audiocassette 312_1426)
  - Leonard Peltier, Otay Prison, Leavenworth, Undated (Box 129, U-matic 312_0594)
  - Liz O'Garvey, Jay Greathouse, La Jolla, California, Undated (Box 131, U-matic 312_0899)
  - Log Sheets for Video Credits and Promos, Undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Log Sheets and Notes for Program Broadcasts, Undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Loxicha, Undated (Box 128, U-matic 312_0579, 312_0580)
  - Malik Interview, Undated (Box 148, Minidv 312_0941)
  - Marco's Message to Freeing the Media, Undated (Box 118, U-matic 312_0470)
    Includes Paper Tiger Opener and Titles
  - Mass Incarceration, Criminal Justice, Undated (Box 149, Minidv 312_1014)
  - Medea OW Narration, Undated (Box 151, Minidv 312_1190)
  - Michael Franti, Undated (Box 153, Minidv 312_1294)
    Label notes: "freezes often"
    Shot by Billy Mitchell; Content includes Concert for peace
  - Midland meeting, last words, Undated (Box 162, Minidv 312_1971)
  - Mike Hoffman, Undated (Box 160, Minidv 312_1707)
  - Military Recruitment B-roll for Brian Drolet, Undated (Box 151, Minidv 312_1213)
  - "Moving Visions", Undated (Box 151, Minidv 312_1197)
    With Liz Canner, Digital Public Art, Arlington, VA
  - MTI #2, Undated (Box 160, Minidv 312_1714)
  - MTI #4, Undated (Box 160, Minidv 312_1705)
  - Nadja Safity, Undated (Box 159, Minidv 312_1685)
  - New Jersey Healthcase #3, Undated (Box 119, U-matic 312_0481)
  - NGO Coordinating Meeting; UN Post-bombing; ICP General Secretary and GC Members, Undated (Box 151, Minidv 312_1177)
  - "Not My President", Undated (Box 134, Dvcam 312_1055)
  - "Not My President!" "Voices From the Counter Coup", Undated (Box 89, U-matic 312_0115)
  - "Not TV" Segment for History Project, Undated (Box 147, Minidv 312_0870)
    Content includes Seona's videocard for history project
  - Occupation Watch -- "Privatizing Iraq", Undated (Box 134, Dvcam 312_1044)
  - "One Stripe", Undated (Box 157, Minidv 312_1575)
  - "Only the Beginning: Roz Payne", Undated (Box 151, Minidv 312_1198)
  - Operation Ceasefire GFX, Undated (Box 161, Minidv 312_1805)
    With Martyn Green, AIM; Content includes Main Titles, Iraq Photo Doc/Facts, Iraq Civilian Casualties, Atom Bombs Test, Main titles with sound
  - "Operation Desert Song", Undated (Box 155, Audiocassette 312_1425)
    New York City War Resisters League Local
  - "Our House: Gays and Lesbians in the Hood" -- Production File -- Black Planet Productions, Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Palestine Rally, DC, Undated (Box 152, Minidv 312_1251, 312_1252, 312_1253)
  - "Peace and War" Programs, Undated (Box 152, Minidv 312_1233)
  - Pete Seeger, Undated (Box 149, Minidv 312_1005)
  - Pic the Homeless, Undated (Box 155, Minidv 312_1427)
  - Pratap Chatterjee Interview, Iraq, Undated (Box 153, Minidv 312_1293)
    Label notes: "bad sound"
    Content includes interview about Business and war: financial reconstruction after war; private companies training Iraqis in democracy; weapons makers, reconstruction companies; Halliburton, security; changes in Iraqi lives
  - Producers' Reel, Undated (Box 119, U-matic 312_0473)
  - Producers' Reel, Undated (Box 131, U-matic 312_0898)
    Content includes Opening Titles, Closing Credits, Promos (6), Regional Promos (11), Stay Tuned (5)"
  - Production Graphics -- Alison's New Graphics, Undated (Box 147, U-matic 312_0893)
    Content includes Kids, Labor, Housing
  - Production Graphics -- Animations for Second Series, Undated (Box 138, U-matic 312_1418)
    Animations titled "Farming and Mass Media vs Popular Culture" by Allison Morse, "On Tape" by Nan Toskey, "Access, Images, and Housing"
  - Production Graphics -- Countdown, Open, End Credits, PSAs, Undated (Box 131, U-matic 312_0895)
    Content includes Countdown, Open, End Credits - slow, medium, fast, PSAs: "Kids in Park," "Peace if More Access Channels," "To Stay Informed," "Current Events"
  - Production Graphics -- Credits, Undated (Box 159, Minidv 312_1684)
  - Production Graphics -- DDTV Opening, Undated (Box 161, Minidv 312_1815)
  - Production Graphics -- Deep Dish II Intro, Undated (Box 131, U-matic 312_0900)
  - Production Graphics -- Graphics 3, Undated (Box 119, Betacam sp 312_0476)
  - Production Graphics -- Intro, Undated (Box 131, U-matic 312_0903)
    Content includes Access Edits - DIVA; Levis; Miss Saigon; Scarlot Harlot at 2:38
  - Production Graphics -- Layered Intro, Undated (Box 131, U-matic 312_0904)
  - Production Graphics -- Mark Reed Voice Overs, Undated (Box 160, Minidv 312_1703, 312_1717, 312_1719)
  - Production Graphics -- Old Deep Dish Graphics, Undated (Box 132, Vhs 312_0906)
  - Production Graphics -- Reuters Edit, Undated (Box 138, Dvcam 312_1743)
  - Production Graphics -- "Rock, Paper, Missiles," Logos, Undated (Box 152, Minidv 312_1232)
  - Production Graphics -- TV Drawings, Undated (Box 131, U-matic 312_0897)
    Content includes Children's drawings of TV
  - Production Graphics -- Women's Logos, Titles for shows, Central America, Undated (Box 131, U-matic 312_0901)
  - Production Graphics -- WYBE Logo, Deep Dish Open, Series Credits, Undated (Box 131, U-matic 312_0896)
  - Production System Layout Diagram, Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - "Protect Me From What I Want", Undated (Box 147, Minidv 312_0918)
  - Protests and Arrests, Undated (Box 153, Minidv 312_1273)
  - Psychiatrist, sit-in protest, interviews, Undated (Box 151, Minidv 312_1173)
  - "Race Against Prime Time", Undated (Box 136, U-matic 312_1395, Box 137, U-matic 312_1404)
    Produced and directed by David Shulman, New Decade Productions
    U-matic tape 312_1404 was identified as moldy by the Media Preservation Unit. This item is currently isolated from other items in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, the Preservation department should be contacted ASAP. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - "Rock Down Central America", Undated (Box 137, U-matic 312_1411)
    U-matic tape 312_1411 was identified as moldy by the Media Preservation Unit. This item is currently isolated from other items in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, the Preservation department should be contacted ASAP. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - Sabra and Shahla from Daily Motion, Undated (Box 156, Minidv 312_1483)
  - "Salam," Sacramento, Undated (Box 147, Minidv 312_0886)
    Content includes several Muslims talking about Islam, terrorism, American view of Islam, prison camp abuse, and the desicration of the Quran
  - SAM Tribunal, Undated (Box 148, Minidv 312_0928, 312_0929, 312_0930, 312_0931, Box 149, Minidv 312_1004)
  - "The Seventh Voyage of Sinbad", Undated (Box 142, Betacam sp 312_1874)
  - Skeleton Rag, Undated (Box 152, Minidv 312_1215)
  - "Somalia: Kill To Feed", Undated (Box 136, U-matic 312_1394)
  - "Spoon", Undated (Box 151, Minidv 312_1211)
  - "Stereotype," Joonwoo, Ahn, Undated (Box 156, Minidv 312_1527)
  - Suzy Schneider, Undated (Box 132, U-matic 312_0974)
    Content includes 2 takes: 1 with bomb intro, 1 with FEMA intro
  - "Taking Back America: NDP and the Nation", Undated (Box 151, Minidv 312_1203)
  - "There's No Place Like Home", Undated (Box 138, U-matic 312_1417)
  - Third Camera, Undated (Box 160, Minidv 312_1711)
  - Tikkun Public School, October 12-13 (Box 147, Minidv 312_0878, 312_0881, Box 157, Minidv 312_1577, 312_1578, 312_1579)
  - "Tropic of Chaos", Undated (Box 157, Minidv 312_1573, 312_1574)
  - "Undocumented and Unafraid" Union Square Demonstration, New York City, Undated; cuid39523 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_397)
  - USSF Children, Undated (Box 155, Minidv 312_1433)
  - "Wall Street, Good Guy or Bad Guy?", Undated (Box 138, U-matic 312_1416)
    Great Western Entertainment Corporation
  - "War of Aggression", Undated (Box 148, Minidv 312_0937)
  - War Resisters League, Undated (Box 152, Minidv 312_1263)
    Content includes Different directors, ex-staff, volunteers, etc. talking about plans for RNC 2004 demonstrations; UPN also films
  - "What the Hell is Wrong in the United States?", Undated (Box 148, Minidv 312_0942)
  - "Whose Agenda Is It Anyway?", Undated (Box 153, Minidv 312_1324)
    With Dina Mendros and Julia Moreno
  - Wikileaks at BPFA, Undated (Box 155, Minidv 312_1435)
- Series II. Administrative Files, 1982-2017; 23.5 Linear Feet in 37 manuscript boxes and 5 flat boxes; 2.39 Gigabytes in 1,807 files
  Series II. Administrative Files (1982-2017) is arranged chronologically with documents grouped together by content type.
  Series II. Administrative Files (1982-2017) contains paper and digital files created during the day to day activities and administration of Deep Dish TV, including Board of Directors and Steering Committee meeting minutes, memoranda, and notes; financial documents such as budgets and expense reports; fundraising strategy and related documentation such as merchandise sales and grant applications; mail received from viewers and mailing lists for outgoing communications; contact lists for research and outreach on a variety of subjects; carriage lists detailing the television stations that carry Deep Dish TV programs; and internal staff correspondence, job descriptions, and staff biographies.
  - Management Assistance Group -- Consultant Services, 1982-1991 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Contact Lists -- Press and Media Organizations, circa 1983-1986 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Contact Lists -- NFLCP Access Centers, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Contact Lists -- Press and Labor Organizations, circa 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Contact Lists -- Press Book and Phone Log, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Contact Lists -- Mailing Addresses, 1986-1988 (Box 14, Folder 4, 5)
  - Contact Lists -- Media Organizations, circa 1987 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Contact Lists -- National Alliance of Media Arts Centers, circa 1987 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Contact Lists -- "Deeplist", July, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Contact Lists -- Mailing List, July, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Contact Lists -- Alternative Press Center Database, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Contact Lists -- Press, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Contact Lists -- Mailing List, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Contact Lists -- Press and Media Organizations, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Contact Lists -- Mailing Addresses, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Contact Lists, Spring 1990 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Contact Lists, Fall 1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Contact Lists -- Not Channel Zero College Screenings, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Contact Lists -- Press, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Contact Lists -- Community Based Organizations, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Contact Lists -- Corporation for Public Broadcasting Directory, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Contact Lists -- New York Public School Districts, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Contact Lists -- SCOLA Affiliate List, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Contact Lists -- Affinity Organizations and Affiliates, 1991-1994 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Contact Lists -- Mailing Addresses, 1991-1996 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Contact Lists -- Outreach for 1992 Summer-Fall Series (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Contact Lists -- Visual Art and Advertising Vendors, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Contact Lists -- Deep Dish TV Database, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Contact Lists -- Message Log, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Contact Lists -- Not Channel Zero Media Contacts, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Contact Lists -- Public Access Listings, 1993-1999 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Contact Lists -- Press Organizations and Journalists, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Contact Lists -- Telephone Contacts, circa 1994 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Contact Lists -- Healthcare Outreach, circa 1994 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Contact Lists -- Alliance for Community Media, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Contact Lists -- National Campaign to Stop Control Unit Prisons Mailing List, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Contact Lists -- Paper Tiger Phone Lists, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Contact Lists -- Mailing Addresses, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Contact Lists -- Programming Contacts, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Contact Lists -- Event Participant Lists, 2000-2014; cuid39531 (Box 17, Folder 5, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_236)
  - Contact Lists -- TV Database, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Contact Lists -- Phone Message Log, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Contact Lists -- Radio Contacts, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Contact Lists -- Production and Fundraising Contacts, 2006-2010; cuid39559 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_234)
  - Contact Lists -- Email Contacts, 2006-2018; cuid39560 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_235)
  - Contact Lists -- Actors, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Contact Lists -- Media Conferences, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Contact Lists -- Middle East Studies Association, 2008; cuid39561 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_237)
  - Contact Lists -- Sign-up Sheets and Address Labels, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Contact Lists -- Cable Affiliates, 2008-2009; cuid39562 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_238)
  - Contact Lists -- Deep Dish TV Program Producers, 2009-2011; cuid39563 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_239)
  - Contact Lists -- Scholars, 2009-2011; cuid39564 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_240)
  - Contact Lists -- Active Native American Producers, Undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Contact Lists -- Black Student Unions, Undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Contact Lists -- The Bureau of Indian Affairs List of Tribal Leaders, Undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Contact Lists -- Business Cards, Undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Contact Lists -- Deep Dish Interns and Staff, Undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Contact Lists -- Media Organizations, Undated (Box 17, Folder 19, Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Foundational Planning Documents, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Program Submissions, 1985-2008 (Box 18, Folder 3, 4)
  - Expenses -- Boston Film / Video Foundation, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Expenses, 1987-2011 (Box 18, Folder 6, 7, Box 19, Box 20)
  - Expenses -- Electric Film, 1990-1995 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Expenses -- Vyvx Services, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Expenses, 2004-2012; cuid39565 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_241)
  - Deep Dish TV Project Proposal, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Dish Installation Photos, circa 1986 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Photos of the Deep Dish Crew, circa 1986-2016; cuid39532 (Box 21, Folder 2, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_242)
  - Carriage Lists, 1986-1996 (Box 21, Folder 3, 5, 7, 9, Box 22, Folder 3, 6, 7, 9)
  - Carriage Lists -- Deep Dish Cooks Up a Second Series, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Carriage Lists -- Feedback Forms, Spring 1990 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Carriage Lists -- Station Informational Packets, 1990-1992 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Carriage Lists -- Behind Censorship Station Call Letters, Feb-May, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Carriage Lists -- PBS HotList, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 1)